Lesson 6.
第6课。
Smash and grab.
砸碎并抓住。
Piccadilly: n.   皮卡迪利大街
The expensive shops in a famous near Piccadilly were just opening.
一家著名的皮卡迪利附近昂贵的商店刚刚开业。
arcade: n.   有拱廊的街道（两旁常设商店）
At this time of the morning, the arcade was almost empty.
在早晨的这个时候，街机几乎是空的。
Mr. Taylor.
泰勒先生。
ring: n.   戒指
The owner of a jewelry shop was admiring a new display.
一家珠宝店的所有者正在欣赏新展示。
Two of his assistants had been working busily since 8 o'clock and had only just finished.
他的两名助手从8点开始就忙于工作，刚刚完成。
necklace: n.   项链, ring: n.   戒指, background: n.   背景
Diamond necklaces and rings had been beautifully arranged on a background of Black Velvet.
钻石项链和环在黑色天鹅绒的背景上精美布置。
After gazing at the display for several minutes, Mr. Taylor went back into his shop.
凝视着展示的几分钟后，泰勒先生回到了他的商店。
The silence was suddenly broken when a large car.
一辆大车突然破裂了沉默。
arcade: n.   有拱廊的街道（两旁常设商店）, ring: n.   戒指, headlight: n.   （汽车等）前灯
With its headlights on and its home blaring, roared down the arcade.
大灯亮着，房屋吹来，咆哮着街机。
It came to a stop outside the jewelers.
它停在珠宝商外面。
One man stayed at the wheel while two others with black stocking over their faces jump out
一个男人呆在方向盘上，另外两个人脸上有黑色的袜子跳了出来
and smashed the window of the shop with iron bars.
并用铁杆砸碎了商店的窗户。
While this was going on, Mr. Taylor was upset.
在此过程中，泰勒先生不高兴。
staff: n.   全体工作人员
He and his staff began throwing furniture out of the window.
他和他的员工开始将家具扔到窗外。
arcade: n.   有拱廊的街道（两旁常设商店）
Chairs and tables went flying into the arcade.
椅子和桌子飞入街机。
One of the thieves was struck by a heavy statue.
其中一个小偷被一个沉重的雕像击中。
But he was too busy helping himself to diamonds to notice any pain.
但是他忙于帮助自己去钻石，注意到任何痛苦。
raid: n.   偷袭
The raid was all over in three minutes.
突袭在三分钟内结束了。
scramble: v.   爬行, fantastic: adj. 非常大的
For the men scrambled back into the car and it moved off at a fantastic speed.
对于这些人来说，爬上了汽车，它以惊人的速度移动。
Just as it was leaving, Mr. Taylor rushed out and ran after it throwing astrays in
就在离开时，泰勒先生冲出了
faces.
面孔。
But it was impossible to stop the thieves.
但是不可能阻止小偷。
They had got away with thousands of pounds worth of diamonds.
他们逃脱了数千磅的钻石。